# KEVIN ANTONIO CORRALES MORENO

# INGENIERO DE SOFTWARE

#### CONTACTO

+505 84935993

kevinantonioc13@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-corrales-44a9731aa/

#### HABILIDADES

Lenguajes de programación

JavaScript, TypeScript, C#

Bases de datos

• SQL server, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Stack front-end

· React, Vue 3, Tailwind

Stack back-end

• NodeJS, Express, .NET

Control de versiones

• Git, Github, Azure DevOps

EDUCACION

# UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL DE INGENIERIA (UNI)

2019-2023

CS50x

2023

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WrH NCyNVNmS4MSK3T7wzLtg8HPzzVB zM/view?usp=sharing

-----

PORTAFOLIO

https://kevg1t-portfolio.netlify.app/

#### PERFIL

Soy un apasionado desarrollador web con una sed insaciable de conocimiento y una profunda pasión por crear experiencias digitales excepcionales. Mi viaje en el mundo del desarrollo web comenzó como un entusiasta autodidacta, lo que me ha convertido en un firme creyente en el poder de la autodisciplina y la autoeducación.

EXPERIENCIA

**FULL STACK** 

2024 - activo

**Grupo LAFISE** 

Proyecto canales alternos ServiRED(2.0)

Responsabilidades.

- Desarrollo y mejoras de módulos en FrontOffice y BackOffice de la aplicación.
- Gestión y comprensión de procesos transaccionales.
- Desarrollo y exposición de nuevos endpoints, servicios y procesos en las APIS consumidas por la aplicación.
- Corrección de Bugs y errores mediante herramientas como AWS Cloudwatch y Opensearch.

## **DESARROLLADOR FRONT-END**

2023 - 2024

Coderland by dominion

Pasantía como desarrollador.

Responsabilidades.

- Desarrollo de componentes, funcionalidades e interfaces con react y vue 3.
- Mantenimiento a código ya existente.

LENGUAJES

Ingles: Basico

Español: Nativo

# KEVIN ANTONIO CORRALES MORENO

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

+505 84935993

kevinantonioc13@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-corrales-44a9731aa/

#### SKILLS

Programming languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, C#

#### **Databases**

• SQL server, MySQL, PostgreSQL

#### Stack front-end

. HTML, CSS, React, Vue 3, Tailwind

#### Stack back-end

Node js, Express, .NET

#### versions control

· Git, Github, Azure DevOps

#### EDUCATION

# UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL DE INGENIERIA (UNI)

2019-2023

CS50x

2023

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WrH NCyNVNmS4MSK3T7wzLtg8HPzzVB zM/view?usp=sharing

#### PORTFOLIO

https://kevg1t-portfolio.netlify.app/

#### PROFILE

I'm a passionate front-end web developer with an insatiable thirst for knowledge and a deep passion for creating exceptional digital experiences. My journey in the world of web development began as a self-taught enthusiast, which has made me a strong believer in the power of self-discipline and self-education.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **FULL STACK**

2024 - active

#### **Grupo LAFISE**

ServiRED alternate channels project (2.0)

#### Responsibilities

- Development and improvements of modules in FrontOffice and BackOffice of the application.
- Management and understanding of transactional processes.
- Development and exposure of new endpoints, services and processes in the APIS consumed by the application.
- Correction of bugs and errors using tools such as AWS Cloudwatch and Opensearch.

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

2023 - 2024

#### Coderland by dominion

Internship as a developer.

# Responsibilities

- Development of components, functionalities and interfaces with react and vue 3.
- Maintenance to existing code.

# LANGUAGE

English: Basic

Spanish Native